Guide to the Duke University Press Records, 1812-2019 UA.07.08.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University Press records
1812-2019
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University Press
UA.07.08.0002
487 Linear Feet
2.98 Gigabytes
Duke University Press publishes both scholarly books and journals, primarily in the humanities and social sciences. In its early years, preference was given to works published by faculty, graduate students and alumni and to works focused on southern states. The records of Duke University Press span from 1812-2019 and consist of correspondence, annual catalogs, advertisements, annual reports, Board minutes, contracts and agreements, book and journal reviews, financial records, marketing files, the records of former director Steve Cohn, and facsimiles of the Carlyle letters.
Access Restrictions
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
Provenance
The Duke University Press Records were received by the University Archives as a series of transfers from 1956-1993, 2010, 2016, 2017, 2018, and 2019.
Historical Note
The origins of Duke University Press date back to 1892 and the establishment of the Trinity College Historical Society. In 1921, the Trinity College Press was officially founded. William T. Laprade served as the first Director until 1926. That same year, Duke University Press was founded with William K. Boyd as Director. Following Boyd as Director were the following: Paul F. Baum (1927-1930), J. Fred Rippy (1930-1936), Henry Dwire (1936-1944), Laprade (1944-1951), Ashbel G. Brice (1951-1981), Richard C. Rowson (1981-1989), Lawrence J. Malley (1989-1993), Stanley Fish (1993-1998), and Steve Cohn (1998-2019).
Duke University Press publishes approximately 120 books annually and more than 30 journals. It publishes primarily in the humanities and social sciences and issues a few publications for primarily professional audiences (e.g., in law or medicine). It is best known for its publications in the broad and interdisciplinary area of theory and history of cultural production.
Collection Overview
The records are arranged in the following series: Director's files, Editorial Advisory Board, Editorial files, Author files, Subject files, Financial records, Catalogs, the Association of American University Presses, the Carlyle Letters, Marketing Files, and Steve Cohn Papers. The collection consists of correspondence, annual catalogs, advertisements, Board minutes, annual reports, contracts and agreements, book and journal reviews, financial records, correspondence, art and publicity related to the marketing of publications, and facsimiles of the Carlyle letters. The material ranges in date from 1812-2019.
Much of the contents list for the Editorial Files, Marketing Files, Steve Cohn papers, and Executive Support shared email were provided by Duke Press and have not been arranged or described by the Duke University Archives.
Related Material
Bernard I. Duffey Papers, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
South Atlantic Quarterly Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
William Thomas Laprade Papers, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Thomas and Jane Welsh Carlyle Papers, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to some portions of this collection is restricted; materials require additional screening for sensitive or personnel information. Contact Research Services for new information.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection contains electronic records that must be requested and accessed in our reading room. Contact Research Services with questions.
Journals (Periodicals); Journals (Periodicals); Journals, Scholarly; Journals, Scholarly; Rippy, J. Fred (James Fred), 1892-1977; Rhine, J. B. (Joseph Banks), 1895-1980; Rippy, J. Fred (James Fred), 1892-1977; Association of American University Presses; Rhine, J. B. (Joseph Banks), 1895-1980; Carlyle, Jane Welsh, 1801-1866; Association of American University Presses; Brice, Ashbel; Carlyle, Jane Welsh, 1801-1866; Duke University -- History -- 20th century; Brice, Ashbel; Carlyle, Thomas, 1795-1881; Duke University -- History -- 20th century; Duke University Press; Carlyle, Thomas, 1795-1881; Laprade, William Thomas, 1883-1975; Duke University Press; Laprade, William Thomas, 1883-1975; Dwire, Henry R.; Dwire, Henry R.
- Director Files, 1932-1990; 1
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists primarily of the Director's correspondence. Unlike other series, the Director's files are arranged by accession due primarily to the presence of two very different periods of time.
  Accession A56-699 contains correspondence from 1932-1957, covering the tenures of J. Fred Rippy (1930-1936) and Henry Dwire (1936-1944), and W. T. Laprade (1944-1951). Both Dwire and Laprade were named Acting Director while also serving as Editor of the South Atlantic Quarterly, a journal published by the Press. The correspondence for this period covers both the Press and the SAQ. Overall, the correspondence focuses primarily on getting books to press and requests to publish books/articles. Correspondents include Clement Eaton, J. B. Rhine, and Daniel C. Roper. Of particular interest is the correspondence during the 1940s, showing how the Press handled the cutbacks and financial burdens of the war years.
  Accession A93-54 contains subject files during the 1980s. Subjects include American Literature journal, budget, staff memos, and Friends of the Press.
  - Director's Files, 1932-1936 (Box 1)
  - Director's Files, 1937 (Box 1)
  - Director's Files, 1938 (Box 1)
  - Director's Files, 1939 (Box 1)
  - Director's Files, 1940 January-July (Box 1)
  - Director's Files, 1940 August-December (Box 1)
  - Director's Files, 1941 January-July (Box 1)
  - Director's Files, 1941 August-December (Box 1)
  - Director's Files, 1942 January-April (Box 1)
  - Director's Files, 1942 May-August (Box 1)
  - Director's Files, 1942 September-December (Box 1)
  - Director's Files, 1943 January-June (Box 1)
  - Director's Files, 1943 July-December (Box 1)
  - Director's Files (Folklore Collection), 1943-1948 (Box 1)
  - Director's Files, 1944 January-June (Box 1)
  - Director's Files, 1944 July-December (Box 1)
  - Director's Files, 1945 (Box 1)
  - Director's Files, 1946 (Box 1)
  - Director's Files, 1947 January-May (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, 1947 June-December (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, 1948 (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, 1949 (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, 1950 January-June (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, 1950 July-December (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, 1951 January-June (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, 1951 July-December (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, 1952 January-June (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, 1952 July-December (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, 1953 January-June (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, 1953 July-December (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, 1954 January-June (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, 1954 July-December (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, 1955 January-June (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, 1955 July-December (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, 1956 January-June (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, 1956 July-December (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, 1957 January-September (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, undated (Box 2)
  - Director's Files (Reports/Contracts), 1941-1942 (Box 2)
  - Director's Files, American Literature, 1986-1988 (Box 3)
  - Director's Files, Budget, 1983 (Box 3)
  - Director's Files, Budget Review Meeting w/ University Officers, 1986 March 20 (Box 3)
  - Director's Files, Committee on the Future of the South Atlantic Quarterly (Box 3)
  - Director's Files, In-house Computers, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Director's Files, Meeting w/ Dick Stubbing, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Director's Files, Report to the Chancellor, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Director's Files, Special Projects Request, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Director's Files, Staff memos, 1981-1984 (Box 3)
  - Director's Files, Joanne Ferguson, 1984-1989 (Box 3)
  - Director's Files, Susan Kuc, 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Director's Files, John Menapace, 1981-1984 (Box 3)
  - Director's Files, Jim Roberts, 1985-1988 (Box 3)
  - Director's Files, Daniel J.J. Ross, 1984-1989 (Box 3)
  - Welty, Eudora (Box 3)
  - Friends of the Press, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Friends of the Press, i.e. Board of Visitors, Editorial Advisory Board, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Friends of the Press, 1989-1990 (Box 3)
- Editorial Advisory Board, 1939-2001; 2
  Records included in this series are minutes, correspondence and subject files of the Editorial Advisory Board of the Press. The Board was established by an action of the University Trustees in 1926. Original responsibilities included selecting the Director, approving budgets, giving final approval on manuscripts, advising on staffing, establishing policies, and supervising periodical publications.
  Some discrepancies on the exact title of the Board can be seen throughout this series. The Board was established as the Editorial and Administrative Board and is also referred to as the Duke Press Board. Moreover, the Board has also been considered a standing University committee.
  - Editorial Advisory Board, 1944-1953 (Box 3)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, 1954-1955 Spring (Box 3)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, 1955 October-1956 Spring (Box 3)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, 1956 December-1957 Spring (Box 3)
  - Editorial Advisory Board Meeting, 1957 October 1 (Box 3)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, 1958 February-May (Box 3)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, 1958 October-November (Box 3)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, 1959 March-1960 December (Box 3)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, 1971 May-1974 June (Box 3)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, 1980 March 19-1987 March 23 (Box 3)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, 1987 April 27-1989 November 27 (Box 3)
  - Editorial Advisory Board (Duplicates), 1984-1989 (Box 3)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, Chairman's Files, 1960-1962 (Box 3)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, Chairman's Files, 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, Chairman's Files, 1962-1964 (Box 3)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, Chairman's Files, 1964-1966 (Box 4)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, Chairman's Files, 1963-1965 (Box 4)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, Chairman's Files, 1965 (Box 4)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, Correspondence, 1952-1957 (Box 4)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 4)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, circa 1939-1952 (Box 4)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, 1950-1961 (Box 4)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, Retreat, 1985 February 9 (Box 4)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, South Atlantic Quarterly Correspondence, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, Special Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Policy and Procedure Setting Meeting of EAB, Dec-82 (Box 69)
  - EAB Presentation on Journals, 1983 March 25 (Box 69)
  - Special EAB: President's House, 1984 January 14 (Box 69)
  - Special EAB meeting, 1985 February 09 (Box 69)
  - Special EAB Meeting, 1986 February 07 (Box 69)
  - Special EAB Meeting (at President's house), 1987 February 14 (Box 69)
  - 2/11/88 (5:30 pm), 1988 February 11 (Box 69)
  - Sp EAB Mtg, 1989 (Box 69)
  - EAB discussion of Journals Special issues and approved needs, 1989 (Box 69)
  - Special EAB Mtg, 1990 February 10 (Box 69)
  - EAB Special, 1991 February 02 (Box 69)
  - EAB Minutes, 1990-1993 (Box 69)
  - EAB Special Mtg, 1993 January 30 (Box 69)
  - Sp EAB Mtg and Aftermath, 1994 April 28 (Box 69)
  - EAB Mtg Minutes, 1995 (Box 69)
  - EAB Minutes, 1996 (Box 69)
  - Mtgs, pre-Review to discuss Bk sales at SYP, 1995-1998 (Box 69)
  - EAB Minutes, 2001-2002 (Box 69)
  - EAB Membership Lists, 2000-2006 (Box 69)
  - EAB Efforts to secure more mkt. funding, 1989-1990 (Box 69)
  - EAB Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 69)
  - EAB Minutes, 1997 (Box 69)
  - EAB Minutes, 1998 (Box 69)
  - EAB Minutes, 1999-2000 (Box 69)
  - EAB Financial Presentation, 2000-2001 (Box 69)
- Editorial Files, 1944-2016; 3
  Materials in this series related to specific works published by Duke Press and contain information related to the editorial process. Materials were not processed by University Archives staff, and this inventory was provided by the Duke University Press in 2016-2018. There is likely significant overlap between this series and the Editorial Advisory Board, Author Files, and Marketing Files series.
  The majority of this series is arranged alphabetically by author.
  Materials from UA2018.0061 related to PCI & SSN Project and Book Project Acquisition Files are in this series, interfiled alphabetically in this inventory.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access is restricted; materials require additional screening before use. Contact Research Services for more information.
  - Blackburn, William B., (One and Twenty), 1944-1945 (Box 4)
  - Cahoon, John B., (Formulating X-Ray Technics), 1940-1967 (Box 4)
  - Davis, Helen Miller, (Constitutions, Treaties, Electoral Laws of States in the Near and Middle East), 1950-1952 (Box 4)
  - DeConde, Alexander, (Isolation and Security), 1956-1958 (Box 4)
  - DeConde, Alexander, (Entangling Alliances and The Secretary of State), 1956-1967 (Box 4)
  - Durden, Robert F., (James Shepherd Pike: Republicanism and the American Negro, 1850-1882), 1953-1975 (Box 4)
  - Durden, Robert F., (Reconstruction Bonds and 20th Century Politics: SD v NC), 1960-1962 (Box 4)
  - Hendricks, W.C., (Bundle of Troubles and Other Tarheel Tales), 1943-1944 (Box 4)
  - Hubbell, Jay B., (The South in American Literature), 1952-1959 (Box 4)
  - American Literature (journal), Hubbell and Gohdes, eds., 1950-1958 (Box 4)
  - American Literature (journal), C. Gohdes, ed., 1954-1968 (Box 4)
  - Ecological Monographs (journal), 1928-1959 (Box 4)
  - Ecology (journal), 1947-1963 (Box 4)
  - Hispanic American Historical Review (journal), C. Griffin, ed., 1953-1954 (Box 4)
  - Hispanic American Historical Review (journal), L. Hanke, ed., 1954 (Box 5)
  - Hispanic American Historical Review (journal), L. Hanke, ed., 1955 (Box 5)
  - Hispanic American Historical Review (journal), L. Hanke, ed., 1956-1960 (Box 5)
  - Hispanic American Historical Review (journal), L. Hanke and D. Worcester, eds., 1956-1963 (Box 5)
  - Southern Association Quarterly (journal), 1947-1949 (Box 5)
  - Kuznets, Moore and Spengler, (Economic Growth: Brazil, India, Japan), 1955-1963 (Box 5)
  - Leary, Lewis, (Articles on American Literature), 1946-1955 (Box 5)
  - Leary, Lewis, (The Literary Career of Nathaniel Tucker), 1950-1951 (Box 5)
  - Macdonald, Allan Houston, (Richard Hovey, Man and Craftsman), 1955-1972 (Box 5)
  - Mansergh, Nicholas, (Commonwealth Perspectives), 1958 (Box 5)
  - Tilley, Nannie M., (Guide to the Manuscript Collections in the Duke University Library), 1947 (Box 5)
  - White, Newman I., (Frank C. Brown's Folklore), 1947-1951 (Box 5)
  - White, Newman I., (Frank C. Brown's Folklore), circa 1951-1952 (Box 5)
  - White, Newman I., folder one (Frank C. Brown's Folklore), circa 1952-1957 (Box 5)
  - White, Newman I., folder two (Frank C. Brown's Folklore), circa 1952-1957 (Box 5)
  - Woodress, James L., (Dissertations on American Literature/Howells and Italy), 1952-1957 (Box 5)
  - Inquiries/Surveys, 1946-1947 (Box 5)
  - Inquiries/Surveys, 1948-1949 (Box 5)
  - Monthly Book Sale reports, 1952-1958 (Box 5)
  - Monthly Book Sale reports, 1959-1961 (Box 5)
  - Reports (including Annual Reports), 1932-1950 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence w/ Seeman Printery Inc., 1946-1949 (Box 5)
  - Aaron Bobrow Strain, 2005-2007 (Box 283)
  - Aaron Fox, 1994-2006 (Box 270)
  - AAUP Exchange, 1986-1989 (Box 348)
  - AAUP Exchange, 1994 (Box 348)
  - Abadie, Roberto: The Professional Guinea Pig, 2007-2010 (Box 227)
  - AbdouMaliq Simone, 2000 (Box 268)
  - Abdur-Rahman, Aliyyah; The Erotics of Race, 2007-2012 (Box 100)
  - ABT Books CD ROM Publishing Project, 1989 (Box 320)
    Correspondence and advertising materials
  - Acland, Charles and Wasson, Haidee: Useful Cinema, 2007-2011 (Box 242)
  - Acland, Charles: Swift Viewing, 2005-2012 (Box 249)
  - Acosta, 1997-2003 (Box 305)
  - Adair, 1993 (Box 340)
  - Adam Knee, 2004-2005 (Box 283)
  - Adams, 2000-2003 (Box 260)
  - Adams, 2006-2010 (Box 325)
  - Adams Cleruens, 2002-2005 (Box 270)
  - Adams, Carol: Animals and Woman, 1994 (Box 160)
  - Adams, Jan: A Foreign Policy in Transition, 1988-1994 (Box 191)
  - Adams, Vincanne; Markets of Sorrow, 2011-2013 (Box 105)
  - Adrianapetryna, 2004-2006 (Box 259)
  - Ads & Reviews (Box 337)
  - ADS & Reviews (Box 338)
  - Aers, 1991 (Box 340)
  - Afzal-Khan, Fawzia Seshadri-Crooks, Kalpana: The Preoccupation of Postcolonial Studies, 1992-2001 (Box 140)
  - Agrawal, 2003-2006 (Box 260)
  - Agrawal, Arun: Greener Pastures, 1996-1999 (Box 191)
  - Ahmed, Sara: On Being Included, 2009-2012 (Box 249)
  - Ahmed, Sara; Willful Subjects, 2011-2013 (Box 89)
  - Aiken, Susan Barker, Adele: Dialogues/Dialogi, 1991-1994 (Box 191)
  - Akcan, Esra; Modernity in Translation, 2007-2011 (Box 100)
  - Alan Shepard, 1990-1991 (Box 329)
  - Alan Tansman, 2003-2009 (Box 333)
  - Alaska Native Reader, 2005-2008 (Box 304)
  - Albanese, Denise: The New Science and its Others, 1994-1996 (Box 191)
  - Alberto Acereda and Will Derusha, 2003 (Box 96)
  - Albuquerque Permissions, 2013-2014 (Box 89)
  - Albuquerque, Durval Muniz, 2013 (Box 89)
  - Aldama, Arturo: Disrupting Savagism, 1997-2001 (Box 218)
  - Aldrin, Andrew: Soviet Space Policy manuscript, 1989 October 5 (Box 320)
    Correspondence
  - Alexander Dent, 2004-2009 (Box 333)
  - Alexander Jacqui, 2001-2006 (Box 259)
  - Alexander, Irving: Personology, 1985-1990 (Box 191)
  - Alexander, Robert: The History of International Trotskyism, 1987-1993 (Box 160)
  - Alexandra Hadias, 1997-2003 (Box 268)
  - Alexis McCrossen, 2005-2009 (Box 326)
  - Ali, 1999-2005 (Box 259)
  - Allen, Chad: Narrative as Blood/Blood as Narrative, 1999 September 3-2001 November 15 (Box 510)
    Proposal, reader reports and correspondence
  - Allen, Jafari: Venceremos, 2003-2012 (Box 242)
  - Allen, Tony; An Autobiography of the Master Drummer of Afrobeat, 2011-2013 (Box 111)
  - Allison, Anne; Precarious Japan, 2012-2013 (Box 111)
  - Allworth (ed.): Tatars of the Crimea: Return to the Homeland, 1997-2000 (Box 344)
    Reviews, correspondence, and marketing materials
  - Allworth, Edward A.: The Tears of Crimea, 1987-1997 (Box 160)
  - Allworth, Edward: Central Asia, 1997-1994 (Box 191)
  - Allworth, Edward: Central Asia Book Series, 1984-1989 (Box 192)
  - Allworth, Edward: Central Asia Book Series, 1983 (Box 192)
  - Allworth, Edward: Tatars of the Crimea, 1994-1985 (Box 191)
  - Allworth: Review Slip F97, 1997 (Box 344)
    Review slip for National Past-Times
  - Alvarez, Sonia; Translocalities, 2009-2011 (Box 118)
  - Alvarez, Sonia; Translocalities; Permissions, 2010-2013 (Box 118)
  - A Lydia Maria Child Reader Ads and Reviews, 1998 (Box 343)
  - Amar, Paul; The Security Archipelago, 2007-2013 (Box 111)
  - Amelie Hastie, 2004-2006 (Box 278)
  - American Enterprise Institute, 1984-1986 (Box 286)
  - Amie Parry, 1997-2009 (Box 289)
  - Amin, Ash; Political Openings, 2010-2012 (Box 105)
  - Amin, Ash; Political Openings; Contracts, 2012 (Box 105)
  - Amoore, Louise; The Politics of Possibility, 2011-2013 (Box 111)
  - Amoore, Louise; The Politics of Possibility; Arts and Permissions, 2013 (Box 111)
  - Amoore, Louise; The Politics of Possibility; Contracts, 2012-2013 (Box 111)
  - Amy Villarejo, 2002-2004 (Box 274)
  - Ana Delsarto, 1999-2003 (Box 305)
  - Anagnost, 1997-1999 (Box 349)
  - Anagnost, Ann: National Past-Times, 1994-1997 (Box 131)
  - Anagnost: Ads and Reviews, 1997-1998 (Box 344)
    Proposal, reviews, correspondence, and marketing materials relating to National Past-Times
  - Anagnost: Review Slip F97, 1997 (Box 344)
  - Anand Pandion, 2005-2010 (Box 326)
  - Ancona, Ronnie: Time and the Erotic in Horace's Odes, 1993 March 2-1994 October 28 (Box 307)
  - Andaldua, Gloria E, edited by AnaLouise Keating: Light in the Dark/Luz en lo Oscuro, 2013-2014 (Box 364)
    Fall 2015 title
  - Anderson Warwick, 2001-2004 (Box 267)
  - Anderson, Jack: The American Dance Festival, 1982-1988 (Box 160)
  - Anderson, Jack: The American Dance Festival-Photo Info, 1982-1988 (Box 160)
  - Anderson, Jean: Durham County, 2009-2010 (Box 235)
  - Anderson, Jean: Durham County's Centennial History, 1987-1990 (Box 160)
  - Anderson, Patrick: So Much Wasted, 2007-2010 (Box 227)
  - Anderson, Paul: Deep River, 1997-2001 (Box 160)
  - Anderson, Warwick, Jenson, Deborah and Keller, Richard: Unconscious Dominions, 2008-2011 (Box 242)
  - Andolina, 2006-2010 (Box 322)
  - Andrade, Susan: The Nation Writ Small, 1998-2011 (Box 242)
  - Andrea Giunte, 2001-2007 (Box 279)
  - Andrea Smith, 2002-2008 (Box 293)
  - Andrew Hewitt, 2002-2003 (Box 512)
  - Andrews, 2005-2010 (Box 296)
  - Andrews, 2003-2008 (Box 305)
  - Andrews, 1990 (Box 340)
  - Andrews, Edna: Markedness Theory, 1980-1992 (Box 160)
  - Aneesh (Box 272)
  - Aneesh, A.: Neutral Accent: How Language, Labor, and Life Become Global, 2010-2015 (Box 358)
    Spring 2015 title
  - Angela, 1988 (Box 330)
  - Ania Loomba (Box 512)
  - Anker Contract, 2011-2013 (Box 89)
  - Anker; Elizabeth, 2013-2014 (Box 89)
  - Ann Johnson, 2004-2009 (Box 308)
  - Ann Stoler, 2000-2004 (Box 282)
  - Ann Zulawski, 2004-2006 (Box 289)
  - Anna Lorpepsis, 1990 (Box 330)
  - Annamarie, 2003-2006 (Box 262)
  - Anne, Enke, 2005-2006 (Box 262)
  - Annie Coombes (Box 260)
  - Anthes, Bill: Hocke E Aye VI: Edgar Heap of Birds, 2012-2015 (Box 364)
  - Anthony Pinn, 2003-2009 (Box 326)
  - Antliffe, Mark: Avant-Garde Fascism: The Mobilization of Myth, Art, and Culture in France, 1909-1939, 2002 March-2006 May 11 (Box 510)
  - Antoinette BuRTON, 2000-2003 (Box 263)
  - Anzaldva, 2004-2008 (Box 322)
  - Apostolidic, Paul: Stations of the Cross, 1997-2000 (Box 140)
  - Appadurai, Arjun: Globalization, 2000-2003 (Box 154)
  - Applewhite Jim, 2004-2006 (Box 259)
  - Aptekar, Lewis: Street Children of Cali, 1988-1990 (Box 160)
  - Arac, Jonathan Ritvo, Harriet: Macropolitics of Nineteenth-Century Literature, 1993-1994 (Box 192)
  - Aravamudan, Srinivas: Tropicalizations, 1996-2000 (Box 149)
  - Archibald, Robert: Why on Earth are There Business Cycles?, 1990 (Box 320)
    Correspondence and excerpt
  - Ardizzone, Maria: Machine Art and Other Writings, 1993-1997 (Box 192)
  - Argun, 2001 (Box 272)
  - Ari-Chachaki, Wasker; Earth Politics, 2011-2013 (Box 118)
  - Ari-Chachaki, Wasker; Earth Politics; Permissions, 2012 (Box 118)
  - Ariel Poetry, 2001 (Box 513)
  - Armatta, Judith: Twilight of Impunity, 2006-2010 (Box 227)
  - Armus, Diego: The Ailing City, 1997-2010 (Box 235)
  - Arondekar (Box 322)
  - Aronowitz, Stanley: False Promises, 1989-1992 (Box 160)
  - Arrom, Silvia: Controlling the Poor, 1998-2001 (Box 160)
  - Arteaga, Alfred: An Other Tongue, 1992-1996 (Box 131)
  - Arthur Knight, 1999-2002 (Box 262)
  - Arthur Miller, 1990-1991 (Box 330)
  - Asher, 1999-2001 (Box 266)
  - Asher, Kiran (Box 322)
  - Aso, Noriko; Public Properties, 2010-2013 (Box 111)
  - Atkins, E. Taylor: Blue Nippon, 1999-2003 (Box 218)
  - Aubin David, 2005-2010 (Box 325)
  - Auerbach, Jonathan: Dark Borders, 2009-2011 (Box 235)
  - Auerbach, Jonathan: Male Call, 1995-1998 (Box 134)
  - Austen, Jake: Flying Saucers Rock 'n' Roll, 2008-2012 (Box 243)
  - Auyero Javier, 2001-2003 (Box 265)
  - Auyero, Javier: Patients of the State, 2010-2011 (Box 249)
  - Auyero, Javier: The Politics of Survival, 1998-2002 (Box 160)